Guide to the Leonard Solomon Silk papers, 1929-1995 and undated, bulk 1950-1985 RL.01187
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession 6096, 1933-1985, and undated, 86 boxes
  - Papers (Box 117)
    - Trustee Response in 1977 Survey on CED's Future Research, May 31, 1978., plus attachment (Box 117)
    - Work and Nonwork in the Economic System, May 23, 1978 (Box 117)
    - Technology Policy in the USA, Design for Analysis, May 5, 1978 (Box 117)
    - Community Reinvestment Fund, undated (Box 117)
    - Crotty, J. R., Post-Keynesian Economic Theory: An Overview and Evaluation, prepared for 92nd Annual Meeting, American Economic Association, December 28-29, 1979 (Box 117)
    - The Divergent Impact of the Recent Inflation on Various Groups in the United States: A General Survey and Analysis of the Long-term Implications, December 1975 (Box 117)
    - Egypt Background Paper, undated (Box 117)
    - The Establishment: The Committee for Economic Development, 1979, annotated (Box 117)
    - Feiwel, G. R., Different Perceptions of the Economy and Alternative Policy Choices, 1977, preliminary draft (Box 117)
    - Garwin, R. L., Discussion Draft, Issues Paper on Energy Pricing Policy, September, 29, 1975, plus attachments (Box 117)
    - Gintis, H., Neo-Classical Welfare Economics and Individual Development, Cambridge, MA, URPE, July, 1970, Occasional paper, no. 3 (Box 117)
    - Houthakker, H., The Need for Structure Reform, excerpts from a paper ... April 8-9, n.y (Box 117)
  - Papers (Box 118)
    - Humphrey, N. K. [editor], Staff Papers, Washington, D.C., International Monetary Fund, vol. 28, no. 2, July, 1971 (Box 118)
    - International Energy Supply: A Perspective from the Industrial World, Rockefeller Foundation, May, 1978, working paper (Box 118)
    - Jobs for the Hard-to-Employ: New Directions for a Public-Private Partnership, November 3, 1977, draft of statement (Box 118)
    - Lekachman, R., Academic Wisdom and Union Reality, AEA, 1972 (Box 118)
    - Leontief, W., Observations on Some of the World-Wide Economic Issues of the Coming Years, October, 1977 (Box 118)
    - Levenson, D., et al., The Political Economy of the Bote, September, 1977, second draft (Box 118)
    - Lewis, W., A., The Evolution of the International Economic Order, undated (Box 118)
    - Loescher, Samuel M., Limiting Corporate Powers, August 30, 1978, paper presented at Joint Meeting of American Economics Association and Association for Evolutionary Economics, Chicago, IL (Box 118)
    - McCloy, J. J., et al., Inflation and Economic Policy, New York, Model, Roland and Co., Inc., 1966, papers (Box 118)
    - Manning, W. Jr., The Supply of Prime-Time Entertainment Television Programs, Stanford, CA, Center for Research in Economic Growth, September 1973, Memorandum 152 (Box 118)
    - Mansfield, E., et al., Social and Private Rates of Return Industrial Innovations, undated (Box 118)
    - Minsky, H. P., Financial Instability Revisted: The Economics of Disaster, June, 1972 (Box 118)
    - Morgenstern, O., The Collaboration Between Oskar Morgenstern and John von Neuhmann on the Theory of Games, 17 pages (Box 118)
    - Moskow, M. H., Corporate Planning and Government, December 2, 1977, preliminary draft (Box 118)
    - Neild, R. R., Pricing and Employment in the Trade Cycle, Cambridge, University Press, 1963, occasional papers, 21 (Box 118)
    - Noll, R. G., and Tilton, J. E., R and D Risk and Firm Size, undated (Box 118)
    - Okun, A. M., and Perry, G. L., Brookings Papers on Economic Activity, Washington, D.C., Brookings Institution, 1975 (Box 118)
    - O'Leary, J. J., The Revolution on the Bond and Mortgage Markets: Implications for Long-Term Interest Rates, New York, U.S. Trust Co., November 21, 1980 (Box 118)
    - n.t., undated, 3 pages, original (Box 118)
    - Owen, B. M., Economics of the First Amendment: Discussion, December 27, 1973, discussion paper (Box 118)
    - Owen, B. M., Waterman, D., and Wechsler, A. [compilers], Mass Communication and Economics: A Bibliography, Stanford, CA, Center for Research in Economic Growth, October 1973, memorandum, 156 (Box 118)
    - Owen, B.M., and Manning, W. G. Jr., The Television Rivalry Game, Stanford, CA, Dept. of Economics, July 1973, report no. 5 (Box 118)
    - Phillips, A., The Arts, Economics and Policies: Four National Perspectives, New York, Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1975, occasional paper (Box 118)
    - Rees, Alber, Improving Productivity Measurement, December 28, 1979 (Box 118)
    - Revitalizing America's Cities: Vol. I: An Approach to Federal Urban Policy, November 1, 1977 (Box 118)
    - The Rockefeller Foundation, New Religious Movements in America [New York], Rockefeller Foundation, September, 1979, working papers (Box 118)
  - Papers (Box 119)
    - Rosse, J. N., Owen, B. M., and Grey, D. L., Economic Issues in the Joint Ownership of Newspaper and Television Media, May, 1970 (Box 119)
    - Rosse, J. N., Studies in the Economics of Mass Communication, Stanford, CA., Research Center in Economic Growth, April, 1971, memorandum no. 109 (Box 119)
    - Senators Nelson, et al., Tax Reduction and Tax Reform Package, undated (Box 119)
    - Silk, Leonard S., The Business Economist and the Academic Economist, paper to be delivered at 39th Annual Conf. of Southern Economic Assoc. St. Louis, Missouri, November 13, 1969 (Box 119)
    - The Education of Businessmen, New York, Committee for Economic Development, undated, Supplementary paper no. 11 (Box 119)
    - The Relationship Between the United States and Western Europe, (incomplete, 22 pages) (Box 119)
    - Slater, J.E., Governance, New York, Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1976, occasional paper (Box 119)
    - Status of Projects of the Subcommittee on Improving the Long-term Performance of the U.S. Economy, December 2, 1977 (Box 119)
    - Leonard, S. Jr., Securing the Seas: Soviet Naval Challenge and Western Alliance Options, Washington, D.C., The Atlantic Council of the United States, October, 1978, policy paper (Box 119)
    - Thurow, L. C., The Indirect Incidence of Government Expenditures, Cambridge, MA, November, 1979 (Box 119)
    - Tobin, J., and Brainard, W. C., Asset Markets and the Cost of Capital, New Haven, CN, Cowles Foundation for Research in Economics at Yale University, 1977, Cowles Foundation paper no. 440 (Box 119)
    - Tobin, J., How Dead is Keynes?, July 12, 1977, discussion paper, 458 (Box 119)
    - Monetary Policies and the Economy - The Transmission Mechanism, June 14, 1977, discussion paper, 456 (Box 119)
  - Periodicals (Box 119)
    - AR: American Review, The Magazine of New Writing, no. 18, September, 1973 (Box 119)
    - The Atlantic, vol. 242, no. 2, August, 1978 (Box 119)
    - The Bell Journal of Economics, vol. 10, no. 1, Spring, 1979.; vol. 10, no. 2, Autumn, 1979 (Box 119)
    - Brookings Bulletin, vol. 14, nos. 1 and 2, Spring-Summer, 1977 (Box 119)
    - Business Week, no. 2447, August 10, 1976; no. 2663, November 17, 1980; no. 2664, November 24, 1980 (Box 119)
    - California Management Review, vol. XXII, no. 4, Summer, 1980 (Box 119)
    - Challenge, The Magazine of Economic Affairs, vol. 23, no. 5, November / December, 1980 (Box 119)
    - Columbia Journalism Review, March / April, 1975 (Box 119)
  - Periodicals (Box 120)
    - CQ, Economic Affairs, June 5, 1976; June 19, 1976; June 26, 1976; July 10, 1976 (Box 120)
    - ", Senate Tax Bill..., August 14, 1976 (Box 120)
    - Congressional Quarterly, Weekly Report, Vol. XXXIV, no. 26, June 26, 1976 (Box 120)
    - Daedalus: Journal of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences, Vol. 93, no. 3, Summer, 1964; Vol. 95, no. 1, Winter, 1966; Vol. 98, no. 4, Fall, 1969 (Box 120)
    - Data Resources, Inc., European Bulletin, May, 1980 (Box 120)
    - The Data Resources Review of the U.S. Economy: Vol. VI, no. 7, July, 1977; Vol. VII, no. 4, April, 1979 (Box 120)
  - Periodicals (Box 124)
    - Public Relations Quarterly, Vol. 22, no. 2, Summer, 1977 (Box 124)
    - Tempo, vol. 21, no. 2, 1975 (Box 124)
    - Trialogue, A Bulletin of North American - European - Japanese Affairs, no. 13, Winter, 1976-1977; no. 14, Summer, 1977; no. 15, Fall, 1977; no. 16, Winter, 1977-1978; no. 17, Spring, 1978; no. 20, Summer, 1979 (Box 124)
    - Union for Radical Political Economics, vol. 2, no. 2, Summer, 1970; August, 1970 - Special issue (Box 124)
    - The University of Chicago Record, Vol. XIV, no. 4, October 10, 1980, 2 copies (Box 124)
    - World Business Weekly, October 1, 1979; November 24, 1980 (Box 124)
  - Photographs (Box 124)
    - 7 - 8 1/2 x 11, proof sheets of photographs, 35 mm, Middle East, November 8, 1977, black and white (Box 124)
    - 2 - 8 1/? x 11, proof sheets of photographs, 35 mm, Communist China, May 20, 1979, black and white (Box 124)
  - Proceedings (Box 124)
    - American Bankers Association, The Federal Budget in a Dynamic Economy, Proceedings of a Symposium, April 2, 1968 (Box 124)
    - Isard, W., Cumberland, J. H., Regional Economy Planning, papers and proceedings of the 1st Study Conference ... Bellagio, Italy, June 19th to July 1st, 1960 (Box 124)
    - Jacoby, N. H., editor, The Business Government Relationship, Proceedings of a Seminar at University of California, Los Angeles, January 24-25, 1974 (Box 124)
    - Tax Foundation, Inc., Capital, Taxes, and Jobs, Proceedings of Tax Foundation's 27th National Conference, 1976 (Box 124)
  - Programs (Box 125)
    - Allied Social Science Association Program, Chicago, Conrad Hilton Hotel, August 29-31, 1978 (Box 125)
    - Annual Breakfast Meeting of the New York Congressional Delegation with the Board of Directors, Savings Association League of New York State, March 9, 1978 (Box 125)
    - Fall Executive Seminar, November 30 - December 3, 1977, Camelback Inn, Scottsdale, Arizona (Box 125)
    - The Future Role of Business in America, a 3 day conference in San Francisco, May 1-3, 1977 (Box 125)
    - Our World in Transition, American Council of Life Insurance, 5th Annual Meeting, New York City, November 16 to 19, 1980 (Box 125)
    - Professional Fellowships for Journalists and Editors, Pittsburgh, PA, Carnegie-Mellon University, February 5-April 15, 1978, 4 copies (Box 125)
    - Quoque Public Library's Sunday Celebrity series, Mr. Silk, guest speaker, February 17, n.y (Box 125)
    - Social and Ethical Implications of Science and Technology Conference, University of New York, December 7, 8, and 9, 1977 (Box 125)
  - Reports (Box 125)
    - Adam, G. and Rosenthal, S. Z., Report: The Invisible Hand, Questionable Corporate Payments Overseas, 1976 (Box 125)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, Report for 1978 (Box 125)
    - Bank of Canada, Annual Report of the Governor to the Minister of Finance and Statement of Accounts for the Year, 1979 (Box 125)
    - Bank of Israel, Annual Report, 1976, Jerusalem, May 1977 (Box 125)
    - Barton, J.H., et al, Nondiscriminatory Access to Cable Television Channels, Stanford, MA, Stanford University Press, 1973 (Box 125)
    - Basche, J. R. Jr., Unusual Foreign Payments: A Survey of Policies and Practices of U.S. Companies, A Research Report, 1976 (Box 125)
    - The Brookings Institution, Toward Peace in the Middle East, Report of a Study Group, 1975 (Box 125)
    - Buchholz, R. A., Business Environment/Public Policy, summary report, 1975 (Box 125)
    - Committee for Economic Development, Report of the Research and Policy Committee, May, 1978, plus attachment (Box 125)
    - Community Based Organizations in Manpower Programs and Policy, A Conference Report, October, 1977 (Box 125)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, Annual Report, July 1, 1971-August 31, 1972 (Box 125)
  - Reports (Box 126)
    - Crotty, J. R., and Rapping, L. A., The 1975 Report of the President's Council of Economic Advisors: A Radical Critique, 1975 (Box 126)
    - Durbin, E., Income Maintenance and Income Distribution in The United States, a staff report, August, 1971 (Box 126)
    - EMB (Ltd) The Dollar in the New International Monetary System, October 31, 1977 (Box 126)
    - n.a., Economic Report, The State of South Carolina, 1980, July, 1980 (Box 126)
    - n.a., European Labor Market Policies, A special report of the National Comm. for Manpower Policy, no. 27 (Box 126)
    - Foreign Report, South Africa and Israel Unite to Survive, 2 November, 1977 (Box 126)
    - Ford Foundation, Annual Report, 1977 (Box 126)
    - Gordon, R.A., The Need to Disaggregate the Full Employment Goal, special report, no. 17, January 1978 (Box 126)
    - Greene, J., Regulatory Problems and Regulatory Reform: The Perceptions of Business, a research report from the Conference Board, 1980, report no. 769 (Box 126)
    - Gustafson, T. A., Work, Income, and Retirement of the Aged: Report of a Workshop, August, 1979 (Box 126)
    - Harvard University, Annual Report, 1976-1977, vol. 1 (Box 126)
    - Harvard University, Annual Report, 1976-1977, vol. 2 (Box 126)
    - n.a., Increasing Job Opportunities in the Private Sector, a conference report, no. 29, November 1978 (Box 126)
    - Lipset, S. M. and Schneider, W., The Evaluation of Basic American Institutions with Special Reference to Business, Executive summary report, c.a. 1978 (Box 126)
    - Monthly Report of the Deutsche Bundesbank, vol. 32, no. 10, October, 1980 (Box 126)
    - Morgan Stanley, Annual Review, 1977 (Box 126)
  - Reprints (Box 128)
    - n.a., The Americans Economic Review, Vol. LVII, no. 2, May, 1967, The Journal of the American Economic Association, pp. 522-533 (Box 128)
    - The American Economic Review, vol. LVIII, no. 3, part 1, June, 1968, The Journal of the American Economic Association, pp. 509-514 (Box 128)
    - Boddy, R. and Crotty, J., Class Conflict, Keynesian Policies and the Business Cycle, Review of the Month, vol. 24, no. 5, October, 1974, pp.1-17, plus 1 attached letter (Box 128)
    - Bostian, D. B., Jr., The De-Institutionalization of the Stock Market in American Society, Financial Analysts Journal, November-December, 1973, 16 pages, plus attached letter (Box 128)
    - n.a., Businessman and Bureaucrat: The Evolution of the American Social Welfare System, 1900-1940, Journal of Economic History, vol. XXXVIII, March, 1978, no. 1, pp. 120-142 (Box 128)
    - n.a., The Compressibility of Economic Systems, Zeitschrift fur Nationalekonomie, XXVI Bd., Heft 1-3, pp. 192-193 (Box 128)
    - Davidson, P., Falk, L. H., and Lee, H., Oil, Its Time Allocation and Project Independence, Brookings Papers on Economic Activity, 2:1974, pp. 411-448 (Box 128)
    - Denison, E. F., Accounting for United States Economic Growth, 1929-1969, Washington, D.C., Brookings Institution, undated, pages 79-83, 124-135, xerox (Box 128)
    - Eckstein, O., Economic Prospects to 1980: The October DRI Forecast, The Data Resources, November, 1977, 8 pages (Box 128)
    - Between Fred W. Friendly and Arthur Ochs Sulzeberger, An Exchange of Views, The Wall Street Journal, October 5 and 6, 1978, and are reprinted by the New York Times Company, with permission of the Wall Street Journal, 2 pages, 2 copies (Box 128)
    - n.a., The Exhausting of America, Newsweek Magazine, March 31, 1980, 3 pages (Box 128)
    - Fusfeld, D. R., The Basic Economics of the Urban and Radical Crisis, Conference Papers of the Union for Radical Political Economics, December 1968, reprint no. 1, pp. 55-84 (Box 128)
    - Gans, H. J., Jobs and Services Toward a Labor-Intensive Economy, Center for Policy Research, Inc., September, 1976, 2 pages (Box 128)
    - Hamilton, E. J., Growth of Rigidity in Business During the Eighteenth Century, American Economic Review, vol. XXX, no. 1, March, 1940, pp. 298-305 (Box 128)
    - Jennings, J. Q., Wage Settlements and Productivity, Inflation: Long-Term Problems, Proceedings of the Academy of Political Science, Vol. 31, no. 4 (1975), pp. 129-141 (Box 128)
    - Kramer, M., The National Interest - Conflict over Con-Con, New York Magazine, June 11, 1979, pp. 12-13 (Box 128)
    - n.a., The Listener's Right to Hear in Broadcasting, Stanford Law Review, vol. 22, no. 4, April, 1970, pp. 863-902 (Box 128)
    - McQuaid, K., The Business Advisory Council of the Department of Commerce,1933-1961: A Study in Corporate/Government Relations, Research in Economic History, vol. I (1976) pp. 171-197 (Box 128)
    - Machlup, F., The Price of Gold, Princeton, N.J., Princeton University, September, 1968, Reprints in International Finance, no. 10, pp. 782-791 (Box 128)
    - Manning, B., Thinking Straight About Corporate Law Reform, Reweaving the Corporate Veil, Summer, 1977, 29 pages (Box 128)
    - Modigliani, F., and Papdemos, L., Targets for Monetary Policy the Coming Year, Brookings Papers on Economic Activity, I: 1975, pp. 141-165 (Box 128)
    - Morgenstern, O., The Compressibility of Economic Systems and the Problem of Economic Constants, Zeitschrift fur Nationalokonomie, vol. XXVI/1-3, 1966, pp. 191, 197, 199, 201, 203 (Box 128)
    - Owen, B. M., Public Policy and Emerging Technology in the Media, Public Policy, vol. XVIII, Summer 1970, no. 4, pp. 539-552 (Box 128)
    - Rawls, J., Two Principles of Justice, A Theory of Justice, 1971, pp. 228-273 (Box 128)
    - Sametz, A.W., The Measurement of Economic Growth, Indicators of Social Change, 1968, reprint series, no. 90, pp. 77-96 (Box 128)
    - Schwarzman, D., The Effect of Monopoly on Price, The Journal of Political Economy, vol. LXVII, no. 4, August, 1959, pp. 352-362 (Box 128)
    - The Growth of Sales per Man-Hour in Retail Trade, 1929-1963, Reprint from Production and Productivity in the Service Industries, 1969, pp. 201-235 (Box 128)
    - Silk, Leonard S., Carter and Key Advisers Among the Trilateralists, The New York Times, January 6, 1977, 1 page (Box 128)
    - Whitman, M.V.N., Carter's Trilaterial Conspiracy, The Christian Science Monitor, February 7, 1977 (Box 128)
    - Christopher, R. C., The World's New Cold War, Newsweek, June 16, 1975 (Box 128)
    - Carter's Brain Trusts, Time, December 20, 1976, 1 page (Box 128)
    - Silk, Leonard S., Business Power, Today and Tomorrow, Daedalus, Journal of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences, vol. 98, no. 1, pp. 174-190 (Box 128)
    - The Problem of Communication, The Journal of the American Economic Association, vol. LIV, no. 3, May, 1964 (Box 128)
    - The Role of the Business Corporation in the Economy and Society, Economic Systems and Public Policy, by Smith, R. S. and deVyver, F. T., 1966, pp. 83-103 (Box 128)
    - n.a., Special Analysis P, Research and Development, Special Analyses, Budget of the United States Government, 1979, pp. 305-329 (Box 128)
    - U.S. Dept. of Labor, Bureau of Labor Statistics, Employment Structure and Trends, Chapter 3, 'Employment, Hours, and Earnings,' Handbook of Methods, Bulletin 1910, pp. 26-42 (Box 128)
    - n.a., The World and Amitai Etzioni, Center for Policy Research, Inc., September, 1976, 2 pages (Box 128)
  - Speeches, Addresses, Statements, Remarks, Testimony (Box 128)
    - Atkinson, R. C., Dr., remarks: The Role of Research and Development in Economic Progress, Medals Awards Ceremonies of the Franklin Institute, Philadelphia, PA, November 2, 1977, 13 pages, xerox, 2 copies (Box 128)
    - Baker, D. I., Section 2, Enforcement - The View from the Trench, Fairmont Hotel and Tower, San Francisco, August 16, 1972, 19 pages, mimeo (Box 128)
    - Benjamin, C. G., An Unhurried View of Education's Toll to Copyright Proprietors, 6 pages, xerox, plus 1 attachment (Box 128)
    - Bernstien, E. M., Statement: Subcommittee on Trade Committee on Ways and Means, U.S. House of Representatives, November 3, 1977, 4 pages, carbon (Box 128)
    - Blumenthal, W. M., Remarks by Secretary of the Treasury, The Honorable W. Michael Blumenthal, Bond Blub of New York, November 21, 1977, 6 pages (incomplete), printed (Box 128)
    - Brannon, G. M., statement regarding: Tax Incentives for Electric Power Facility Construction, February 25, 1976, 8 pages, printed (Box 128)
    - Committee for Economic Development (Franklin A. Lindsay, chairman), An Approach to Federal Urban Policy, November 25, 1977, 48 pages, printed, plus attached memorandum (Box 128)
    - Doughery, T. J., Statement of Thomas J. Dougherty, before the Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs, U.S. Senate, December 15, 1967, 61 pages, xerox (Box 128)
    - Erlich, S. Mr., Dinner Address of Minister of Finance, Visit of the USA Secretary of the Treasury W. Michael Blumenthal, 2 pages, xerox (Box 128)
    - Ferguson, J. L., The Boss's Number-One Job, Rotary Area Assembly, October 26, 23 pages, xerox (Box 128)
    - Garwin, R. L., Decontrol of Domestic Crude Oil, December 8, 1975, 4 pages, xerox, plus attached letter (Box 128)
    - Gaumnitz, J. E., statement regarding: Tax Exempt Municipal Bonds, January 28, 1976, 5 pages, printed (Box 128)
    - Grace, J. P., The Assault of Economic Incentive, remarks, Presidents' Night, Financial Executive Institute, Milwaukee Athletic Club, May 20, 1980, 85 pages, printed, plus 1 attached note to Leonard S. Silk, May 27, 1980 (Box 128)
    - Hearing of the New York Times Newspaper Company and Newspaper Guild, #3 Case no. 2-UC-135, etc. Proceedings, 80 pages, incomplete, deposition (Box 128)
    - Horton, J., statement regarding: Tax Exemption of Interest on State and Local Bonds, 2 pages, January 28, 1976, printed (Box 128)
    - Kaufman, H., Reflections on Economic Judgments, Remarks made at the International Club of Washington, D.C., September 28, 1977, 4 pages, printed, plus attached letter (Box 128)
    - Kennan, G. F., A Current Assessment of Soviet-American Relations, Remarks, at meeting of Council on Foreign Relations, Washington, D.C., 22 November, 1977, 14 pages, printed (Box 128)
    - Kennedy, Edward M., Senator, statement of Senator Edward M. Kennedy calling for reforms in the Minimum Tax to End Tax Avoidance by the Wealthy, May 6, 1975, 3 pages, xerox (Box 128)
    - Kissinger, Henry A., The Future of Business and the International Environment, before First Washington Meeting of the Future of Business Project of the Center for Strategic and International Studies, Georgetown University, June 28, 1977, 45 pages, printed (Box 128)
    - Laird, M. R., and Moot, R. C., News Conference at the Pentagon, August 10, 1972, 18 pages, printed (Box 128)
    - Lewis, R. G., More 'Food for Peace' Wheat and Corn to Egypt Help Save Mid-East Oil Supply for U.S., 9 pages, xerox, plus attached letter (Box 128)
    - McKinnon, Ronald, The United States: Mature Creditor or Mercantilist?, n.p., 3 pages, xerox (Box 128)
    - McNulty, J. K., statement regarding: Estate and Gift Taxes, March 23, 1976, 8 pages printed (Box 128)
    - Minksy, H. P., remarks: prepared for the Current Economic Problems and Policies Session, Southern Economic Association, New Orleans, Louisiana, November 3, n.y., 5 pages, mimeo (Box 128)
    - Murphy, T. A., remarks at the Downtown Kiwanis luncheon, Birmingham, Alabama, October 4, 1977, 15 pages, xerox (Box 128)
    - Okun, A. M., The Great Stagflation Swamp, Address to the Economic Club of Chicago, October 6, 1977, 19 pages, xerox (Box 128)
    - Noll, R. G. and Okner, B. A., statement before the Subcommittee on Antitrust and Monopoly of the Senate Judiciary Committee, hearings on S. 2373, the Basketball Merger Bill, March 9, 1972, 83 pages, xerox (Box 128)
    - Palmer, R. E., The Auditor's Role, The Conference Board, June 10, 1976, 9 pages, xerox, plus 1 attachment (Box 128)
  - Speeches (Box 129)
    - Popock, C.C., The Manager in Today's Society, Address to the Sixth International Management Conference of the Asian Association of Management Organizations, of CIOS, Singapore, October 31, 1977, 4 pages. printed (Box 129)
    - Press, F., Dr., remarks at the 144th National Meeting of the American Association for the Advancement of Science, Washington, D.C., February 13, 1978, 16 pages, printed (Box 129)